我再确认一下
So, to be clear,
你要从我们这里叫外送吗
you want delivery from this diner?
我当然知道外送是什么意思啦
Yes, I do know what delivery means.
但你知道大肠杆菌是啥吗
Do you know what E. Coli means?
你住哪里
Where do you live?
如果他要吃这里的东西
If he eats from here,
一个小时后 他会长住厕所里
in his bathroom in about an hour.
需要餐巾纸 餐具
Will you be needing napkins? Utensils?
还是中毒控制中心的电话吗
The number for Poison Control?
好的 祝您长命
Well, good luck.
外送员立刻出发
The delivery boy is on his way.
这太好了
Oh, this is good.
我正需要多运动
I need the exercise.
我感觉我最近身材有点微肿
I feel like I'm getting a little chubby!
你短裤里的"小蚯蚓"也有点"微肿"
Oh, I know. I can see it through those shorts.
我当年在越南也当过外送小哥
I was a delivery boy in Vietnam.
但我通常专门送坏消息给别人
I mostly delivered bad news, like,
比如"那个妓女是人妖"
"That hooker was a dude."
金枪鱼沙拉好了 速度快点啊
Here's that tuna salad-- and hurry.
跟像绑架人后穿着尿布开车跑的那位宇航员
Like that astronaut who drove across the country in a diaper,
路上必困难重重
it's not gonna travel well.
再见啦 喷子们
See you later, haters.
别忘了
And remember,
我不在的时候 厄尔管事
Earl's in charge when I'm gone.
厄尔管事吗
Earl's in charge?
行啊 我有商学文凭
Okay. I have a business degree.
而他是三型糖尿病都有
He had all three types of diabetes.
你选他我完全理解
But I get it.
我大概是二零分钟后回来
I'll be gone for...20.
说到"是[四]二零"
Speaking of 4:20,
麦克斯 想要一起来两口大麻吗
Max, you wanna go smoke some weed?
那位管事的人准备点起一管大麻烟
The man in charge just sparked up a doobie.
宝宝心里明白
But I get it.
宝宝我还马上要爽到呢
And I'm about to get it.
惨了 这餐厅以后都归我管了吗
Oh, no. Am I in charge forever?
谁把老年代步车停自行车道上了
Who the hell parked a Rascal in a bike lane?
是我不好
Uh...that's my bad.
我的"盔头"都差点要撞爆了
It almost destroyed my helmet!
从你的短裤看得出你"龟头"差点撞爆
I know. I can see it through those shorts.
这里是撒糖霜站台
And this is the sprinkle station.
而这个是收银机 总有一天它里面会有钱
And this is the cash register, where there'll be money someday.
这位是麦克斯
And this is Max,
麦克斯自制小蛋糕重要的另一半
the other half of Max's Homemade Cupcakes.
你这部小电影马上就要变限制级了
Your little movie is about to be rated R
因为会有强烈与残暴的暴力画面
for strong, brutal violence.
别拍我了
Stop filming me.
我不是在摄影
I'm not filming.
我是在线上直播[潜望镜]
I'm Periscoping.
这招数不是指你头在下方帮男人"口"
Isn't periscoping when you do mouth stuff on a guy
他在上方的眼睛四处看有没有警察吗
while he keeps a lookout for the cops?
麦克斯 不是所有性爱都要担心有条子好吗
Not all sex has to involve the threat of an arrest, Max.
潜望镜是一款社交软件
Periscope is a social media app
让你能通过网络给粉丝直播影片
that streams live videos to your followers.
我在告诉布鲁克林所有喜欢美食节的人
Tell everyone in Brooklyn who loves food festivals
我们明天也会去布希维克美食节
that we'll be at the Taste of Bushwick tomorrow.
或者你可以跟我进厕所拍我更衣
Or you can follow me into the bathroom while I change,
大家今天就能看到阴毛丛生[布希维克]了
and they can see some bushwick right now.
麦克斯 这是很棒的PR
Max, this is great PR.
这是指"公关"
That's "public relations,"
不是"波多黎各"的缩写
not "Puerto Rican."
我知道上次你很失望
I know you were disappointed
因为我带你去PR研讨班
when I took you to that PR seminar
你没看到波多黎各斗鸡赛
and there were no cock fights.
我对网络唯一有好感的时刻
I liked the Internet when the only thing you could do
是看喵星人萌图
was look at cat pictures
和查约翰·斯塔莫斯到底几岁的时候
and find out how old John Stamos is.
他今年八月就要满53岁了呢
He turned 53 in August!
你知道最悲哀的是什么吗
You know what's sad?
是我这年纪 他已经看不上了
I'm too old to date him.
如果这个软件公关效果这么好
If Periscope is such great PR,
那你到底有多少观众呢
how many viewers did you just have?
一个
One.
但说不定他就是重要的那一个呢
But maybe it was a really important one.
给你潜望镜的演出点个赞 卡洛琳
Really loving your Periscope presence, Caroline!
小的一个也算数嘛
Okay. It's a small build.
我仍深信这款软件对我们生意有好处
I still maintain that Periscoping will be great for our business.
告诉你们 我可是在有"潜望镜"之前
For the record, I was filming my business
就开始拍我裤裆里的"龙巢"了
way before it was called "Periscoping."
大家安安
Hi, everybody!
奥列格 我把干洗的衣服拿回来了
Oleg, I picked up your dry cleaning,
还有个好消息
and good news!
他们成功把你"鸟网"上
They were able to get the raspberry stains
沾到的覆盆子汁洗掉了
out of your banana hammock!
我的老天啊
Oh, Lord.
我去哪找人帮我干洗我的嘴
Now who's gonna dry clean my mouth?
所以你去帮我拿干洗的衣服
So you picked up my dry cleaning
而不是去机场接我堂弟吗
instead of my cousin from the airport?
你堂弟来了吗 奇怪
Your cousin's in town? That's weird.
我手机上没有收到色情狂出没的警告啊
I didn't get an alert on my phone.
苏菲 你怎么能忘了这档事
Sophie, how could you forget?
这就是为啥我们玩数独练脑力
This is why we started doing sudoku.
我还以为你玩"舒笃"这姑娘
I thought you started doing sudoku
是因为她又辣又来者不拒呢
'cause she was hot and willing.
我脑子里有很多事情嘛
I got a lot on my mind.
我在想着怎么设计我们的孩子
I'm trying to design our future baby.
姑娘们 我读到一篇文章
See, girls, I read this article
说你可以旋转精子 来甩掉不良物质
that says you can spin sperm to get rid of the bad stuff.
那孩子父亲就不会是奥列格啦
So Oleg's not gonna be the father?
这是真的
It's true.
有一种新科技
There's a new technology
你可以自己选择孩子的基因
where you can select the baby's genes.
我好怀念可以选牛仔裤[基因]的时候
I miss selecting jeans.
现在我只能去旧衣店3块钱的篮子
Now I just reach into the $3 bin
希望能抽到一条合适的牛仔裤
and hope for the best.
我要把体内的精虫大甩特甩
Well, I'm gonna spin that jazz
直到我能甩出个有绿瞳孔
till I get a girl baby with green eyes
还有詹尼佛·安妮斯顿整过后的鼻子
and Jennifer Aniston's second nose
外加我翘臀的女娃
and--and my butt!
为什么我们就不能用自然的方法受孕呢
Why can't we get pregnant the natural way?
把你按在围栏上搞
Up against a fence.
你好
Hello.
我叫戈塔克
I'm Gortak.
你看起来好眼熟
You look familiar.
你是不是跟《权力的游戏》里的某人有点像
Didn't you rib a dragon on "Game of Thrones"?
戈塔克
Gortak!
我的小堂弟
There's my little cousin.
你好啊
Hi!
他名字听起来好像是做手机壳的材料
I think my iPhone case is made out of gortak.
我是奥列格的太太 苏菲
Hi, I'm Oleg's wife, Sophie.
你真是又高大又可口啊
And you're one tall drink of yak's milk.
宝贝 你懂行
You know it, baby.
他就靠这身高发家致富了
And he's taking that tall right to the bank.
他被签去打职业篮球
Gortak just signed to play pro basketball.
不是吧
No way!
篮球是我最爱的运动
Basketball is my favorite sport,
还有就是屁股撞屁股
next to bum wrestling!
我跟球队要来跟布鲁克林队打
I'm in town for a game against Brooklyn.
布鲁克林队是我的最爱
Brooklyn's my team.
他们弱爆了
They stink.
的确
Yeah, well,
我就对任何弱爆的人事物特有好感
I relate to anybody who's not doing that great.
我叫麦克斯
Hey, I'm Max.
我以前在少管所也打球
I used to shoot around in juvi.
以前我们是纵火犯大战杀人未遂犯
We played arsonists versus attempted murderers.
我也学过不少缎带舞呢
I did a lot of ribbon dancing.
卡洛琳就是专门负责破坏气氛的
Caroline's kind of the Screech of the group.
而现在砸场先生来了
And here comes Mr. Belding.
麦克斯 马上就要上班了
Max, it's almost your shift.
你为什么还没换制服
Why haven't you changed into your uniform?
马上就要春天了
It's almost spring.
你为什么还没变成小蝴蝶
Why haven't you changed into a butterfly?
阿憨 这是我堂弟戈塔克
Han, this is my cousin Gortak.
戈塔克 这是我...
Gortak, this is...
傻逼老板
Jackass boss.
处男
Virgin.
《小矮人大世界》[真人秀]
"Little People, Big World."
你们说的我没有每句都懂
I didn't catch all of that,
但是懂的部分都很让我不爽
but I didn't love what I caught.
奥列格 你跟你太太
Oleg, do you and your Sophie
明晚想来看比赛吗
want to come to the game tomorrow night?
我这里有两张票
I have two tickets.
时候正好
Oh, perfect timing.
就昨天 我不能接近
As of yesterday, I'm allowed
拉拉队员15米距离内的禁令刚结束
to be within 50 feet of cheerleaders.
不行 是这样的
Yeah, no. You know what?
真的很抱歉 但我不去了
I'm sorry. I'm out.
今晚我得一边基因改造一个婴儿
You know, tonight I have to genetically modify a person
一边看《傲骨贤妻》
while I watch "The Good Wife."
要我吧 奥列格
Take me, Oleg!
这是你唯一能听到我对你说这句话的时候
Which is the only time you will ever hear me say that.
好主意啊 麦克斯
Good idea, Max.
带你这样的爷们去 苏菲就不会吃醋
Sophie would be pissed if I took a lady.
麦克斯 那我们的安排怎么办
But, Max, what about our plans?
我可不想一个人去美食节[尝鸡鸡]
I don't want to taste Bushwick alone.
那记住 不要喝超过三杯酒
Then don't have more than three drinks...
还有不要乱上别人的车
And don't get in the back of anybody's Isuzu.
你穿得挺隆重啊
You're pretty dressed up.
你知道美食节只是
You know a food festival is just code
在路边垃圾桶旁站着吃的代号吧
for eating outside next to garbage cans.
或许我该跟你去
Maybe I should come.
想做什么工 就穿什么装
Well, I say, "dress for the job you want."
我也想啊 可是我不知道那些
I would, but I don't know what the people
吃光新口味薯片试吃的人该穿什么
who test out all the new potato chip flavors wear.
起司汉堡味品客薯片
Cheeseburger Pringles?
要了
Yes.
姑娘们
Hey, girls!
看看我的婴儿板
Look at my baby board!
我觉得我们终于接近
I feel like we're finally getting close
我能一试的阶段了
to something I can work with.
我的灵感在去掉
You know, it really started to flow
安·海瑟薇的额头后 就源源而来
once I threw away the Anne Hathaway forehead.
这是我见过最吓人的东西了
That is the scariest thing I've ever seen.
那你应该庆幸你没看到
Oh, well, good thing you didn't see it
有安·海瑟薇额头的版本
with the Hathaway forehead.
我喜欢二号宝宝的样子
I love baby number two, but I don't know.
可是奥列格还是想有个惊喜
Oleg still wants to be surprised.
你何不给我们大家一个美妙的惊喜
Why don't you give us all a nice surprise
去趁他睡着的时候帮他刷个牙呢
and brush his teeth while he's sleeping?
是吧
Right?
来 给你
Oh, right. Here.
麦克斯 奥列格不能去看球赛
Max, Oleg can't go to the game.
我们的门诊预约改到了明天
Our baby appointment got changed to tomorrow,
我们还得继续弄小孩身子的部分
and we got to get working on the baby body.
对了
Oh, you know what?
这让我想到
That reminds me.
能给我一张你巨乳的照片吗
Max, do you have a picture of your boobs?
算了 不用
Oh, you know what?
我跟奥列格要就行了
I'll get it from Oleg.
真不敢相信我有两张票
I can't believe I have two tickets!
我要打给厄尔
Ooh, I'm gonna call Earl.
跟朋友去看球一定很有意思
It'd be fun to go with a friend.
你问问我要不要去是会死吗
Would it hurt you to ask me to go to the game?
你明知道我不会答应
You know I'm not gonna say yes.
你想跟我一起去看球赛吗
Do you want to go to the game?
好
Yes!
我自己都觉得好惊喜呢
Wow, that surprised me too.
这可是真正球员给的贵宾席票
These are VIP tickets from an actual player.
这可能会比美食节还赞
This could be better than Bushwick.
很多明星都会去看球赛
I mean, lots of celebrities go to those games.
传单呢
Ooh! Where are the fliers?
我打赌我们能在那里拉到不少生意
I bet we could get a lot of business there.
不许
No!
不许去那边做生意
We are not doing business!
今晚是去好好玩的
Tonight is supposed to be fun.
我觉得生意很好玩啊 但行吧
Well, I find business fun, but okay.
总有一天 你会欣赏我的干劲
One day, you will appreciate my ambition.
总有天我还会试试吃生菜呢
And one day, I will try lettuce,
但不是今晚
but not tonight.
不带传单
No fliers.
我只是觉得这样错失了良机
I just think this is a missed opportunity.
"错失良机"
"Missed Opportunity"
是我当年当钢管舞女郎的艺名
was my stripper name at the Salty Dog.
我今晚就是不想工作
Look, I don't want to work tonight.
这句话也是我当年的招牌语
Which also happened to be my catchphrase.
这不可能是贵宾席
These can't be VIP seats.
姐好久没有这么上气不接下气了
I haven't been this winded since I climbed
上一次是在夏令营为了爬上上层社会
the social ladder at theater camp.
这位置多好呀
These seats are great!
我通常都是坐在停车场
I usually sit in the parking lot
围着烧垃圾的火 唱着杜沃普摇滚乐
around a trash fire, singing doo-wop.
我从来没有坐过最后一排
It's just, I've never sat in the last row before.
我爸总是确保让我坐上第一排
My father made sure I was always in the front.
百老汇看剧 时装周看秀
Broadway, fashion week,
以及他的庭审
his criminal trial.
我爸也曾让我坐过第一排
My father got me front-row seats
观看他得"爱无能"奖
to the "Inability to Love" awards.
我会试着不念叨这事 但我想说
I'll try and let this go, but I'm just saying,
我们本可以去参加美食节
we could have gone to the Taste of Bushwick,
从那里 也比这里离球场近
and we'd still be closer to the court.
我超爱布希维克美食节
Oh, I love the taste of Bushwick.
我不太喜欢
I don't care for it much.
我是琼 这位是戴安
Hi, I'm June, and this is Dianne.
我们有点像末排之"后"
We're sort of the "Mayors" of section Y.
每场比赛必到
Been to every game.
我是麦克斯 这位是卡洛琳
I'm Max. This is Caroline.
你们要"来根手指"吗
You guys want a finger?
我们只是朋友啦
Oh, we're just friends.
你们要不要这根手指
Do you want a finger?
好啊
Sure.
如果你们有多的 我们就要
We'll take one if you got an extra.
那热狗怎么样
And how 'bout that hot dog?
你还吃吗
You still working on that?
麦克斯 你又不知道这根手指放过哪里
Max, you don't know where that finger has been.
这话什么意思
What do you mean?
它之前放在我车里的一个箱子里
It's been in a box in my car.
是啊 卡洛琳
Yeah, Caroline.
这根手指放进过她的箱子[阴部]
This finger's been in her box
就从车里拿出来了
out in the car.
你是哪部分听不懂啊
What part of that don't you get?
小心
Careful.
这杯啤酒花的钱 比我去年买内衣裤花的钱都多
That beer cost more than I spent on underwear last year.
我不喜欢坐这么靠上
I don't like it up here.
我甚至不喜欢啤酒
I don't even like beer.
容易胀气
It's so bloaty.
拜托 没那么糟啦
Come on. It's not that bad.
是咩
Oh, really?
那为什么那家伙在刮胡子
Then why is that guy shaving?
人家肯定是有一个非常重要的面试
Well, obviously, he's got a very important job interview
应征疯狂列车的列车长
as conductor of the crazy train.
麦克斯 我们的位置就像在贫民区
Max, our seats are in a shanty town.
刚爬楼梯的时候
I think somebody tried to sell me a hubcap
有人还想卖我轮毂盖
on the way up the stairs.
卖你多少钱啊
Ooh! How much?
我能借下你的望远镜吗
Can I borrow those binoculars,
好让我不用看眼前这些烦心事
so I can look at something that's not this?
麦克斯 天啊
Max! Oh, my God!
瞧瞧下面的贵宾席的人
Look at all the VIPs down there.
有人也在那边撒"贵宾尿"呢
Well, someone's "VI-peeing" right over there.
麦克斯 我想下去
Max, I want to be down there.
我知道你需要什么
Oh, I know what you need.
想要来一发"手指"吗
Wanna finger?
瞧
Look!
一对有钱情侣在球场边吵架
A rich couple fighting courtside!
那男的气冲冲地走了
Oh, he's storming off!
那女的也气冲冲地走了
She's storming off!
你应该在"老娘不在乎"台
You should do play-by-play
做实况报道主播
on the "I Don't Care" Network.
走 我们去偷坐他们的位置
Come on! Let's go steal their seats.
什么
What?
我喜欢现在的位置
I like where I am.
我的耳膜已经外凸了
My ears already popped.
凑合坐这里算了
We're settled here.
这就是咱俩不一样的地方 麦克斯
That's the difference between us, Max.
我不会"凑合"
I don't settle...
除非等我42岁了
until I'm, like, 42,
我可能会嫁给一个比我矮的人
and then I might have to marry someone shorter than me.
相反的是 我喜欢凑合
I, on the other hand, love settling.
我小时候的第一句话是 "还凑合啦"
My first words were, "Eh, it's fine."
我们只需进行
Look, all we have to do
聪明的战略性转移
is make a few smart, strategic moves,
就有更好的机会在等着我们
and a better opportunity awaits.
拜托啦
Please?
好啦 抱歉 女士们
All right. Sorry, ladies.
她想让我跟她一起"下去"
She wants me to go down with her.
告诉她你今天头疼不就好啦
Just tell her you got a headache.
要表现得我们本来就是坐贵宾席的主儿
Okay, just act like we belong in the VIP section.
真不敢相信那个加长豪车司机居然拐错弯
I can't believe the limo driver took that wrong turn,
所以我们来晚了
and that's why we're late to the game,
所以 也晚到了座位
and thus, our seats.
你忘了提我们坐"所以"公车来的
You forgot to mention that we took thus bus here.
重点是 我们做到了
The point is, we made it.
我回到了属于我的地方
I am back where I belong.
你能闻到下面的这股铜臭味吗
Can you just smell the money down here?
我觉得那是戈塔克蛋蛋的汗臭味
I think that's Gortak's ball sweat.
两位女士
Hello, ladies
你们居然在比赛第二节才神奇出现
who magically appeared in the second quarter.
我能看看你们的票吗
Can I see your tickets?
干嘛
What?
我去大部分地方 都是凭胸进场的啊
These are my tickets to most places.
我们的票吗 当然可以
Our tickets? Of course.
我先找找包里有没有
Let me just find them in here.
在这里
Here they are!
抱歉上面粘了爆米花
Oh, sorry about the popcorn.
我习惯了
I'm used to it.
有钱人都是猪
You rich people are pigs.
麦克斯 我五年没被人叫过有钱猪了
Max, I haven't been called a rich pig in five years!
这里真是太酷了
This is pretty cool!
我之前跟楼上那个装了一背包
I told that Chinese lady up top
散卖胡萝卜的中国女人说
with the backpack full of loose carrots
我会回去 但现在我不会
I'd be back, but I don't think so.
老天
Oh, my God.
我真应该用潜望镜直播
I should totally Periscope this
好让别人以为我们是大牌
so people think we're big shots.
我们离得好近
We are so close,
感觉鼻子随时会被球砸破
I could get my nose broken by a ball!
那我就可以认识帮你修好破鼻子的整容医生
And I could meet the doctor who fixes your broken nose!
一切都那么水到渠成
Everything is working out!
额滴神啊
Oh, my God.
我们居然跟杰斯和碧昂斯同一排
We are in the same row as Jay-Z and Beyonce!
他们还把女儿布露·艾薇带来了
And they brought Blue Ivy!
真不敢相信我居然看见我们的音乐王室了
I can't believe I'm seeing our royal family!
我也不敢相信我的脚居然能碰到球场
I can't believe I'm touching the court with my feet!
或许我该像狗一样 屁股坐地拖着过场
Maybe I should just drag my butt across it like a dog.
会不会太过分
Is that too far?
额滴天神啊
Oh, my God!
碧昂斯刚才居然跟我四目相对
Beyonce just made eye contact with me!
她每次都能看到我 只要
She sees me every time she looks
往左看[边] 往左看[边]
to the left, to the left.
我应该给他们我们的传单
I should get them one of our fliers.
幸好 我总备有一张应急
Luckily, I always keep an emergency flier.
还备了我旧家的钥匙
That and a key to my old house,
以防最后发现这只是一场梦
in case this all turns out to be a dream.
我也希望你这恶梦会走
That's my dream too.
保姆来了
Ooh! Here comes the nanny.
法兰·卓雪也来了吗
Fran Drescher's here?
不 是他们女儿的保姆
No, Blue Ivy's nanny.
我把传单给她
I'll get her our flier.
不好意思 穿吊裆运动裤的小姐
Excuse me, miss, in the drop-crotch sweatpants!
冲冲冲 还有10秒
Go, go, go! Ten seconds!
等等 小姐留步
Wait! Miss, wait!
能收下这个吗
Can you take this?
-麦克斯 她收下... -冲冲冲
- Max, she took the-- - Go, go, go!
麦克斯 你做了什么
Max, what did you do?
我像个白痴一样 把你带来看篮球赛
I took you to a basketball game like an idiot!
现在我要跑路了
And now I'm about to run.
我们要怎么收场 麦克斯
What is our end game here, Max?
我们是要躲 还是要逃
Are we hiding? Are we fleeing?
我就想知道我们用这么丑的姿势走向哪里
I just want to know what we're ugly-walking toward.
我看起来像是有场可收的人吗
Do I look like a person with an end game?
还有 是你让比赛提前收场
Also, ya ended the game.
先不说愤怒的球迷 好消息是
Angry mob aside, the good news is
我成功把传单交到布露·艾薇的保姆手里
I did manage to get that flier to Blue Ivy's people.
坏消息是 你创造了运动史上最大的灾难
The bad news is you created the biggest disaster in sports
完全赶超魔术师约翰逊脱口秀
since Magic Johnson's talk show.
有人来了
Someone's coming.
你说你想要更多跟随者[粉丝]
Well, you said you wanted more followers.
恭喜你在现实生活中做到了
Now you have them in real life!
我的老天
Oh, my God.
这就是联盟第17强的球队宽衣解带的地方啊
This is where the 17th best team in the league gets naked!
同时也是麦克斯和卡洛琳的葬身之地
And also where it ends for ol' Max and Caroline.
干嘛啦 球员们又不是
What? It's not like the players
比赛一结束就直奔更衣室
come right into the locker room after the game.
妈的
Oh, my God.
球员们的确比赛一结束就直奔更衣室
The players come right into the locker room after the game!
当然我们会在这里
Of course we'd be in here.
倒霉就是咱俩的风格啊
This is so us.
你知道还有什么是咱俩的风格吗
You know what else is so us?
我偷一件他们的球衣
Me stealing one of these jerseys.
我们去更衣室做采访吧
Let's do the interview in the locker rooms.
糟糕 他们要进来了
Crap! They're coming in here.
咱们千万不能因为这事露脸 麦克斯
We can't be the face of this, Max.
会成为布鲁克林人见人恨的店
We'll be the most hated business in Brooklyn.
我还算上了新开的那家有
And I'm including the new breakfast restaurant
代客泊婴儿车的早餐店
with the valet stroller parking.
这就是联盟第17强的球队
This is where the 17th best team in the league
尿尿的地方啊
goes number one!
瞧瞧这些小便斗
And from the looks of it,
看来他们不止在球场上才准头差
their aim isn't good in here, either.
那俩妞真是疯子 伙计
Those girls were crazy, man.
她们害我们输掉比赛
They cost us the game.
我们差点就成为联盟第16强队呢
We were almost the 16th best team in the league.
她们是怎么进入贵宾区的
How did they get into the VIP section?
我对蒂姆·艾伦也抱有一样的疑问
I was wondering the same thing about Tim Allen.
伙计 帮我看看我后背这里
Yo, man, take a look at this thing on my back.
看起来像癌吗
Does it look like cancer?
看起来不只是一颗痣
It just seemed like more than a mole, you know?
老实说 看起来像癌前基底细胞
Actually, it looks like a precancerous basal cell.
我们应该进厕所看 那里的灯更亮
We should get a better look in the light in the bathroom.
这里 这里
Here! Over here.
躲进冰浴缸里
Get in the ice bathtub.
位子够两个人
It's big enough for two.
"够两个人[吃]"
"Big enough for two."
红辣椒餐厅也是这么说他们的椰子奶酪棒
That's what Chili's said about their new coconut mozzarella sticks,
但真是 扯犊子
but--swing and a miss.
你居然去红辣椒餐厅不告诉我
You went to Chili's and didn't tell me?
我怕你在普通餐厅也要求要好位子
I was afraid you'd try to get us a better table.
没错
Oh, yeah.
我绝对会去检查一下那玩意
I'd definitely get that thing checked out.
我得冰敷膝盖
Yo, I got to ice this knee.
他们当然会把冰倒我们身上
Of course they'd pour the ice on us!
这事当然会发生在这里
And of course this would happen here,
因为这是发生在我俩身上
'cause it's the 17th worst thing
第17糟的事情了
that's ever happened to me!
你们俩病了吗
Oh, you two sick?
别靠近我 我可不能生病
Stay away from me. I can't get sick.
一旦当你78岁 只需两天时间
When you're 78, it takes about 2 days
就能从感冒流鼻涕 变到死在家喂猫
to go from sniffles to being eaten by your cat.
我们会好的
We'll be fine...
前提是半颗感冒药能治愈全身体温过低
if half a Tylenol can cure full-body hypothermia.
麦克斯 我觉得你还在生我的气
Max, I feel like you're still mad at me
就因为我想要好位置看球
for wanting more for us than bad seats
想要我们的生意变景气
and a struggling business.
我当然生气
Of course I'm mad!
我好久没试过这么冷了
I haven't been this cold
上一次还是某年冬天我参加《致命捕捞》节目时
since that winter I was on "Deadliest Catch."
我有一垃圾桶不会使用的宝宝脸
I've got a waste can of baby faces I'm not gonna use.
是啊
Yeah.
后来我们决定不设计我们的孩子了
Turns out, we're not gonna design our baby anymore.
但你不是想让孩子有一个精致的下巴
But what about wanting it to have a delicate chin?
以及一条大腿缝吗
And a thigh gap?
姑娘们 我醒悟到
You know, girls, I realized
我只想要一个健康快乐的宝宝
I just want to have a healthy, happy baby.
当我拉芙阿姨失去舌头后
You know, it's like my Aunt Ruffa said
她说了这么一句话
after she lost her tongue, you know...
"米粒又是种需有 米粒误食磨呛着"
"Dou det what dou det, and dou don't det updet."
"命里有时终须有 命里无时莫强求"
"You get what you get, and you don't get upset."
那真是一个成熟的决定
That's a really mature decision.
那医生张口就要6万
The doctor wanted 60 grand.
当然 那也影响了我们的决定
Yeah, that affected our decision too.
或许最好的方式就是让事情
Well, maybe letting things happen naturally
顺其自然
is the way to go.
因为有时你一旦强求
Because sometimes when you force things,
就让一帮身价总计1.3亿美元的球员
you put $130 million worth of basketball players
变成了一群伤兵败将
on the disabled list.